Solley mss., 1888-2006 LMC 2885
Lilly Library
- Automobile Catalogs
  - France
    - Lorraine Dietrich/De Dietrich & Cie., "Lorraine Dietrich"(SE: 9/137), 1913 (Box 3)
    - Lorraine Dietrich/De Dietrich & Cie., "Lorraine Dietrich Automobiles 1914"(SE: 10/138) (Box 3)
    - Lorraine Dietrich/De Dietrich & Cie., "Les Lorraines 1925..."(SE: 11/456), 1924 (Oct. 1) (Box 3)
    - Lorraine Dietrich/De Dietrich & Cie., "Societe Lorraine"(SE: 13/808), c. 1928 (Box 3)
    - Lorraine Dietrich/De Dietrich & Cie., "Automobiles Lorraine Nos Modeles 1931", 1930 (Oct. 1) (Box 3)
    - Lorraine Dietrich/De Dietrich & Cie., "15 et 20 C.V. 6 Cylindres..."(SE: 16/811), 1931–1932 (Box 3)
    - Lorraine Dietrich/Lorraine, "La Voiture qui dure..."(SE: 15/810), 1931 (Box 3)
    - Lorraine Dietrich/Lorraine, "La Lorraine 20 cv la plus belle..."(SE: 17/812), 1932 (Box 3)
    - Lorraine Dietrich/Lorraine, Misc. (Box 3)
    - Matra, Renderings (Box 3)
    - Morris – Leon – Bollee, "Morris – Leon – Bollee", c. 1930 (Box 3)
    - Mors, "Courses de l'Exposition de 1900"(SE: 1/139) (photocopy), 1901 (Box 3)
    - Mors, "Societe Anonyme D'Electricite..."(SE: 3/141), 1906 (Box 3)
    - Mors, "Mors 1910"(SE: 4/142) (Box 3)
    - Mors, "Mors 1913"(SE: 5/143) (Box 3)
    - Mors, "Mors 1914"(SE: 6/144) (Box 3)
    - Mors, "The New 20–h.p. Mors Sporting Type"(SE: 7/457), c. 1922 (Box 3)
    - Mors, "Mors"(SE: 8/458), 1924 (Box 3)
    - Mors, "Mors"(SE: 9/459), c. 1925 (Box 3)
    - Mors, Misc. (Box 3)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Moteur a Petrole Systeme Daimler Panhard"(SE: 1/9), 1891 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Voitures Mecaniques..."(SE: 3/11a), 1894–1895 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard & Levassor"(SE: 4/12), 1898 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard & Levassor"(SE: 5/145), 1901 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard & Levassor", 1905 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard & Levassor 1906" (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "1907 Societe Anonyme..."(SE: 7/147) (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard & Levassor"(SE: 8/148), 1910 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "...et voici le fruit", 1921–1922 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard & Levassor"(SE: 14/462), 1924–1925 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard & Levassor Paris"(SE: 15/463), 1926 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "LA Series 'S' Panhard"(SE: 19/816), 1931 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard 6 CS"(SE: 20/817), 1932 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard 6 DS"(SE: 21/818), 1932 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard"(SE: 25/1124a), 1935 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard"(SE: 26/1125), 1935–1936; (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panoramique 1886–1936 Panhard"(SE: 27/1126) (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard vous Presente la...'Dynamique"(SE: 28/1127), 1937 (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, Photographs (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, Road Tests (Box 4)
    - Panhard & Levassor, Misc (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Voitures Automobiles Peugeot"(SE: 1/13), 1896 (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Societe Anonyme des Automobiles Peugeot Paris", 1903(?) (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Societe Anonyme des Automobiles Peugeot 1906"(SE: 4/152) (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Societe Anonyme des Automobiles Peugeot"(SE: 5/153), 1908 (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Societe des Automobiles Peugeot"(SE: 6/154), 1909 (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Automobiles Peugeot 1913"(SE: 7/155) (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Peugeot 1914"(SE: 8/156), (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Peugeot 1922"(SE: 10/465) (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Peugeot 1923"(SE: 11/466) (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "J'aime ma Peugeot", 1935 (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "601 Peugeot"(SE: 13/1128), 1934 (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "601 Peugeot...", c. 1935 (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "402 Peugeot Enchantment"(SE: 15/1130), 1937 (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Peugeot, L'Aerodynamique"(SE: 16/1131), 1937 (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, "Peugeot 402 legere...", 1938 (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, Photographs (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, Road Tests (Box 4)
    - Peugeot, Misc. (Box 4)
    - Pilain, "Pilain 1913"(SE: 1/157) (Box 4)
    - Prosper Lambert, "Prosper Lambert"(SE: 1/158), c. 1902 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Voiturette Automobile...Renault Freres"(SE: 1/16), 1900 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Renault Freres"(SE: 4/161), 1908 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Renault"(SE: 6/163), 1914 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Renault", 1919–1920; (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Renault", 1923 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Les 6 Cylindres 15. 18/22 & 40 cv"(SE: 11/820), 1927 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Votre Etoile...", 1931 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "L'Automobile de France", 1933 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Six and Eight Cylinder Models", 1934 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Renault 6 Cylindres"(SE: 17/1134), 1939 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Renault 8 Cylindres"(SE: 18/1135) (photocopy), 1939 (Box 4)
    - Renault, "Renault de 1898 a nos jours", 1997 (Dec.) (Box 4)
    - Renault, Road Tests (Box 4)
    - Renault, Misc. (Box 4)
    - Rochet–Schneider, "Automobiles...Album No. 74", 1911-1912 (Box 4)
    - Rochet–Schneider, "Automobiles...Album No. 90"(SE: 2/165), 1913 (Box 4)
    - Rochet–Schneider, "La voiture de Qualite – Album No. 140"(SE: 3/472), 1921-1922 (Box 4)
    - Rochet–Schneider, "La voiture de Qualite – No. 141"(SE: 4/473), 1922 (June 1) (Box 4)
    - Rochet–Schneider, "The Car of Quality – No. 164A"(SE: 5/474), 1925 (Box 4)
    - Rochet–Schneider, "Rochet–Schneider"(SE: 8/826), c. 1930; (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - Rochet–Schneider, Misc. (Box 4)
    - Roger, Misc. (Box 4)
    - Rolland–Pilain, "Rolland–Pilain"(SE: 2/475), 1919–1920 (Box 4)
    - Rolland–Pilain, Misc. (Box 4)
    - Th. Schneider, "Automobiles Th. Schneider", 1913 (Box 4)
    - Serpollet, "Exposition Universelle 1889 Serpollet"(SE: 1/17) (Box 4)
    - Serpollet, "Speedwell Motor and Engineering...", 1902 (Box 4)
    - Simca, Road Tests (Box 4)
    - Sizaire–Berwick, "Sizaire–Berwick"(SE: 2/170), 1913–1914 (Box 4)
    - Sizaire–Berwick, "Sizaire–Berwick 20 H.P."(SE: 3/171), 1914 (Box 4)
    - Sizaire–Berwick, "Sizaire–Berwick"(SE: 5/477), 1920 (Box 4)
    - Sizaire–Berwick, "Sizaire–Berwick Ltd."(SE: 6/478), 1920 (Box 4)
    - Sizaire–Berwick, "Chassis de Hout–Luxe 25 cv"(SE: 7/479), c. 1925 (Box 4)
    - Sizaire–Berwick, "Chassis de Luxe 18 C.V....", 1927–1928 (Box 4)
    - Sizaire–Berwick, Misc. (Box 4)
    - Sizaire & Naudin, "Etablissements..."(SE: 1/172), 1907 (Box 4)
    - Sizaire & Naudin, "Etablissements...Paris Saison 1909"(SE: 2/173) (Box 4)
    - Talbot–Darracq/Talbot, "Voitures Automobiles Electriques", 1897 (Box 4)
    - Talbot–Darracq/Talbot, "Voiture Automobiles Darracq...", 1899 (Box 4)
    - Talbot–Darracq/Talbot, "The Pleasure of Touring in Darracq Cars", 1904 (Box 4)
    - Talbot–Darracq/Talbot, "Les Nouvelles Darracq Ltd.", 1914 (Box 4)
    - Talbot–Darracq/Talbot, "Talbot–Darracq"(SE: 8/480), 1921 (Box 4)
    - Talbot–Darracq/Talbot, "Automobile Talbot"(SE: 9/481), 1925 (Box 4)
    - Talbot–Darracq/Talbot, Road Tests (Box 4)
    - Talbot–Darracq/Talbot, Misc. (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "Publicity Sheet", 1929 (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "Talbot Toujors..."(SE: 11/832), 1930 (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "Talbot", 1931 (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "Talbot Toujours..."(SE: 12/833), 1932 (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "Modeles 1934..."(SE: 13/1137) (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "Talbot l'aristrocrate de l'Automobile"(SE: 14/1138), 1936; (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "Talbot"(SE: 15/1139), 1937 (Mar.) (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "Talbot"(SE: 16/1140), 1937 (Oct.) (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "l'Aristrocrate de l'Automobile"(SE: 17/1141), 1938 (Jan.) (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "Talbot 1939"(SE: 18/1142) (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "The Car from Paris", 1946 (Box 4)
    - Talbot, "La Voiture de Luxe et de Sport Francaise", 1954 (Box 4)
    - Talbot, Photographs (Box 4)
    - Talbot, Road Tests (Box 4)
    - Talbot, Misc. (Box 4)
    - Tracta, "Tracta Roues A.V Motrices"(SE: 1/834), 1928 (Box 4)
    - Tracta, "Tracta Roues A.V. Motrices"(SE: 2/835), 1929 (Box 4)
    - Tracta, "Tracta Front Wheel Drive"(SE: 3/836), 1930 (Box 4)
    - Tracta, "Tracta", 1931 (Box 4)
    - Tracta, "Specs. For Types 'D,' 'E,' 'F' Models", 1930 (Oct.) (Box 4)
    - Tracta, Misc. (Box 4)
    - UNIC, "UNIC", 1935 (Box 4)
    - UNIC, "UNIC", 1937 (Box 4)
    - UNIC, Misc. (Box 4)
    - Voisin, "Carrosseries"(SE: 2/483), 1920 (Box 5)
    - Voisin, "Carrosseries"(SE: 3/484), 1922 (Box 5)
    - Voisin, "Voisin"(SE: 7/488), 1925 (Box 5)
    - Voisin, "Automobiles Voisin"(SE: 9/838), 1928 (Box 5)
    - Voisin, "Voisin"(SE: 10/839), 1930 (Box 5)
    - Voisin, "Voisin Propose la Voiture..."(SE: 12/1144), 1935 (Box 5)
    - Voisin, "Voisin"(SE: 13/1145), 1937 (Box 5)
    - Voisin, "En 1938 Voisin vous Offre"(SE: 14/1146), (2 copies) (Box 5)
    - Voisin, Photographs (Box 5)
    - Voisin, Misc. (Box 5)
    - Berliet, "Automobiles Berliet 1913 Lyon"(SE: 4/77) (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Brasier, "Voitures Automobiles"(SE: 1/2b), 1899–1900 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Bugatti, "Bugatti"(SE: 15/765), 1932 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Delahaye, "Symbole de la qualité Française présente la 235", 1951–1952 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Gobron, "Automobiles Gobron"(SE: 4/120), c. 1912 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Hispano–Suiza, "Advertisement", c. 1920's (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Hispano–Suiza, "H.S. 12 Cylindres 1932"(SE: 16/799) (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Hispano–Suiza, "HS (54 H.P. 12–CYL 1934)"(SE: 19/112) (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard & Levassor 1912 La Marche a l'eitoile" (SE: 9/149) (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Si..."(SE: 10/150), 1913 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard & Levassor"(SE: 13/461a), 1922 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Renault, "Automobiles Renault"(SE: 5/162a), 1911 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Renault, "Renault"(SE: 12/822a), 1928–1929 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Renault, "Renault"(SE: 12/822b), 1928–1929 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Renault, "8 Cylindres Renault"(SE: 16/133), 1935 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Sizaire–Berwick, "Sizaire–Berwick"(SE: 9/829), 1927 (Octobre) (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Hispano–Suiza, "H.S. 12 Cylindres 1932"(SE: 16/799) (Box 29 (Oversize))
    - Hispano–Suiza, "H.S. (54 H.P. 12–CYL. 1934)"(SE: 19/112) (Box 29 (Oversize))
    - Panhard & Levassor, "Panhard & Levassor 1922"(SE: 13/461a) (Box 29 (Oversize))
    - Renault, "Automobiles Renault"(SE: 5/162a), 1911 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Germany
    - Adler, "Salon International…Adler Stand No. 43"(SE: 2/841), 1930 (Box 5)
    - Adler, "Adler baut"(SE: 3/1148) (photocopy–inc.), 1933 (Box 5)
    - Adler, "Adler Cars 1.7 Litre"(SE: 4/1149), 1935 (Box 5)
    - Adler, "Adler Trumpf–Junior 1 liter..."(SE: 5/1150), 1935 (Box 5)
    - Adler, "Adler Sport Wagen"(SE: 6/1151) (photocopy), 1935 (Box 5)
    - Adler, "Adler Junior 1 Ltr. Trumpf..."(SE: 7/1152), 1936 (Box 5)
    - Adler, "Adler–Trumpf–Junior–Sport..."(SE: 8/1153), 1936 (Box 5)
    - Adler, "Adler Diplomat 3 Litres"(SE: 9/1154), 1937 (Box 5)
    - Adler, "Adler 2,5 Liter – Sechszylinder – 58 PS"(SE: 10/1155), 1937 (Box 5)
    - Adler, "Adler 2, 5 Ltr. Stromform"(SE: 12/1157), 1939 (Box 5)
    - Adler, Photographs (Box 5)
    - Adler, Misc. (Box 5)
    - Audi, "Audi 100 PS Acht-Zylinder TU+YP Zickau"(SE: 1/842), 1929 (Box 5)
    - Auto–Union, "Auto Union", c. 1936 (Box 5)
    - Auto–Union, "Wanderer–Kompressor"(SE: 2/1158), 1937 (Box 5)
    - Auto–Union, Renderings (Box 5)
    - Auto–Union, Road Tests (Box 5)
    - Auto–Union, Misc. (Box 5)
    - Benz & Cie., "Maison Parisienne de Voitures Automobiles..."(SE: 5/22), 1890s (Box 5)
    - Benz & Cie., "Salon du Cycle...Systeme 'Benz'"(SE: 7/24), 1898 (Box 5)
    - Benz & Cie., "Benz & Co. Rheinische Gasmotoren–Fabrik..."(SE: 8/25b), 1899 (Oct.) (Box 5)
    - Benz & Cie., Misc. (Box 5)
    - Benz, "Benz"(SE: 14/179), 1913 (Box 5)
    - Benz, "Benz"(SE: 15/180), 1913 (Box 5)
    - Benz, "Benz"(SE: 17/490), c. 1921 (Box 5)
    - Benz, "Automobiles 'Benz' La Premiere Marque..."(SE: 18/491), 1922 (Box 5)
    - Benz, "Benz & Cie"(SE: 19/492), 1924 (Box 5)
    - Benz, Photographs (Box 5)
    - Benz, Renderings (Box 5)
    - Benz, Misc. (Box 5)
    - BMW, "BMW 2 Sportwagen..."(SE: 1/1159), 1936 (Box 5)
    - BMW, "2 Ltr Sport...Sportwagen"(SE: 2/1160), 1937 (Box 5)
    - BMW, "45 PS Kabriolett..."(SE: 3/1161), 1937 (Box 5)
    - BMW, "2 und 3½ Ltr Sechszylinder BMW"(SE: 5/1163), 1939 (Box 5)
    - BMW, Road Tests (Box 5)
    - BMW, Misc. (Box 5)
    - Borgward, Photographs (Box 5)
    - Borgward, Road Tests (Box 5)
    - Borgward, Misc. (Box 5)
    - Golde, "Golde Schiebedacher", c. 1960s (Box 5)
    - Horch, "Der Achtzylinder..."(SE: 1/843), 1927–1928 (Box 5)
    - Horch, "Horch"(SE: 2/844), 1929 (Box 5)
    - Horch, "Horch V12"(SE: 5/847), 1931–1932 (Box 5)
    - Horch, "Horch Auto.Union A–G"(SE: 6/1164), 1932–1933 (Box 5)
    - Horch, "Horch"(SE: 8/1166), 1933 (Box 5)
    - Horch, "Horch 3 Litre – 8 Cylinder – Type 830", 1933–1934 (Box 5)
    - Horch, "Horch 850"(SE: 9/1167), 1935 (Box 5)
    - Horch, [Horch](SE: 13/1171), 1937 (Box 5)
    - Horch, "Horch"(SE: 14/1172), 1937–1938 (Box 5)
    - Horch, Photographs (Box 5)
    - Horch, Road Tests (Box 5)
    - Horch, Misc. (Box 5)
    - Mannesmann, "8 Zylinder 9/55 PS", 1928 (Box 5)
    - Maybach, "Maybach"(SE: 1/848), c. 1927 (Box 5)
    - Maybach, "Maybach Zeppelin 12..."(SE: 6/1177), 1935–1936 (Box 5)
    - Maybach, "Maybach 12' Zeppelin"(SE: 5/1176), 1935 (Box 5)
    - Maybach, "Maybach Type SW 38"(SE: 8/1179), 1937 (Box 5)
    - Maybach, "Maybach TYP SW 38"(SE: 9/1180), 1939 (Box 5)
    - Maybach, Photographs (Box 5)
    - Maybach, Misc. (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes Motor Carriages"(SE: 3/183), 1906 (Jan. 1) (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes"(SE: 5/185), 1909 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes–Daimler = Motoren..."(SE: 7/187), 1910 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes MDM Ltd.", 1912–1913 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes", 1914 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes Automobile"(SE: 10/495), 1916–1917 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Supercharger Models 1886–1928", c. 1920s (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes", 1920 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes"(SE: 13/498), 1923 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes"(SE: 14/499), 1924 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Six Cylinder Mercedes..."(SE: 15/500), 1925 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "What Others Think...", 1925 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Motoring for the Owner–Driver...", 1925 (Aug. 24) (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Super–Charging for Normal Use", 1925 (Dec. 11) (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Lure of Mercedes", 1925 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Specification...33/180 h.p...", 1925–1926 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "24–100 h.p. Mercedes–Weymann...", 1926 (Mar. 3) (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes Supercharger"(SE: 16/501), 1926–1927 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, Photographs (Box 5)
    - Mercedes, Misc. (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "The 33/180 H.P. Mercedes", 1926 (Oct.) (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "1885 Mercedes 1925"(SE: 1/851), 1926–1927 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz"(SE: 2/852), 1928 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes Benz Original Karosserien", 1928 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Model S"(SE: 3/853a), 1928 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz .SSK."(SE: 8/854), 1928 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 630"(SE: 8/856), 1928–1929 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "8 Type 'Nurbourg'"(SE: 8/858), 1930 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Model 'SS'"(SE: 9/859), 1930 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "TYP Mannheim Sport-Ausfuhrung"(SE: 10/860), 1931 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz", 1932 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 'Nurburg' 8 Cylinder 4.9 Litres...", 1932 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "TYP 'Mannheim' Sonder–Cabriolet", 1932 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "TYP SS u. SSK"(SE: 12/862), 1932 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "TYP Mannheim"(SE: 13/1181), 1933 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "TYP 380"(SE: 14/1182), 1933 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "TYP Nurburg"(SE: 15/1183), 1933 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz Cabriolets"(SE: 16/1184), 1933 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz"(SE: 17/1185), 1933 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 200", 1933–1934 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 380"(SE: 19/1187), 1934 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 130"(SE: 18/1186), 1934 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz Cabriolets"(SE: 20/1188), 1934 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 500 mit Kompressor"(SE: 22/1190), 1934 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 150"(SE: 23/1191), 1935 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz Cabriolets"(SE: 21/1189a), 1935 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz Cabriolets"(SE: 21/1189b) (photocopy), 1936 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Typ 170 H", 1936 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Model 500 Supercharged"(SE: 25/1193), 1937 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "TYP 320"(SE: 26/1194), 1937 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 540 K"(SE: 27/1195), 1937 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 540 K"(SE: 29/1197), 1938 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Automobile Manufacturing Program for 1938" (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz"(SE: 31/1199), 1939 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "La Nouvelle Mercedes–Benz Type 170S", 1949; 1950 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "New Mercedes–Benz Type 170S", 1949 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 220 – Convertible A", c. 1950s (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 220", 1952–1953 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 300S", 1952 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 300", 1952–1953 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 300S", 1953 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 300SL", 1955 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 300", 1956 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 300S", 1956 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Type 220S Coupe...", 1957 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "190 SL", 1959 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "220 S/SE Coupe...", 1959 (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Announcing...3.5 Liter V–8s", c. 1970s (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz 220D", c. 1970s (Box 5)
    - Mercedes–Benz, "C–Class Estate", c. 1990s (Box 6)
    - Mercedes–Benz, Photographs (Box 6)
    - Mercedes–Benz, Renderings (Box 6)
    - Mercedes–Benz, Road Tests (Box 6)
    - Mercedes–Benz, Misc. (Box 6)
    - Mollenkamp–werk, "Mollenkamp–werk"(SE: 1/502), c. 1924 (Box 6)
    - Neue Automobile – Gesellschaft Berlin (NAG), "Automobiles N.A.G.", c. 1904–1905 (Box 6)
    - D.A.K., "D.A.K. (Presto, Dux)"(SE: 1/493), c. 1921–1922 (Box 6)
    - NAG, "NAG Sport Modell 208"(SE: 8/865), 1931 (Box 6)
    - NAG, Misc. (Box 6)
    - Porsche, Photographs (Box 6)
    - Porsche, Renderings (Box 6)
    - Rennwagen, Renderings (Box 6)
    - Rohr, "Rohr 8 CYL."(SE: 1/867), 1930 (Box 6)
    - Rumpler, Misc. (Box 6)
    - Simson–Supra, "Simson Supra"(SE: 3/871) (photocopy), 1929 (Box 6)
    - Simson–Supra, "Der Simson–Supra–Achtzylinder"(SE: 4/872), 1931 (Box 6)
    - Simson–Supra, Misc. (Box 6)
    - Stoewer, "Automobiles Stoewer", c. 1912 (Box 6)
    - Stoewer, "Personen–Kraftwagen"(SE: 1/508), 1919 (Box 6)
    - Stoewer, "25 Personen–Kraftwagen"(SE: 2/509), 1921–1922 (Box 6)
    - Stoewer, "Stoewer"(SE: 4/874), 1928 (Box 6)
    - Stoewer, "Stoewer Acht–Zylinder Modelle 1929"(SE: 5/875) (Box 6)
    - Stoewer, "Stoewer Arkona"(SE: 8/1203), 1939 (Box 6)
    - Stoewer, Misc. (Box 6)
    - Veritas, "Veritas", 1950 (Box 6)
    - Volkswagen, Photographs (Box 6)
    - Volkswagen, Road Tests (Box 6)
    - Volkswagen, Misc. (Box 6)
    - Horch, "Horch 8"(SE: 3/845), 1931 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Horch, "Horch 8 – Horch 12"(SE: 4/846), 1931–1932 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Horch, "Horch"(SE: 10/1168), 1936 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Horch, "Horch"(SE: 11/1169), 1936 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Maybach, "Maybach 12 Zeppelin"(SE: 3/850), 1931 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Maybach, "Maybach Typ 5W35 140 PS..."(SE: 7/1178), 1936 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Mercedes, "Mercedes, Grand Prix Cars"(SE: 12/497), 1921 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Adler, "Adler"(SE: 1/840), 1929 (Box 29 (Oversize))
    - Maybach, "Maybach 12"(SE: 2/849), 1929 (Box 29 (Oversize))
    - Mercedes–Benz, "La Grande Mercedes"(SE: 11/861), 1931 (Box 29 (Oversize))
    - Mercedes–Benz, "Mercedes–Benz 600", 1963 (Box 29 (Oversize))
    - Benz, "1912 Benz"(pen and ink rendering by Josh Ferguson), 1949 (Apr. 29) (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Great Britain
    - AC, "AC"(SE: 1/1204), 1936 (Box 6)
    - AC, "AC"(SE: 1/1205), 1937 (Box 6)
    - AC, Road Tests (Box 6)
    - AC, Misc. (Box 6)
    - Allard, "Allard Special V–8 V–12"(SE: 1/1208), 1937; 1939 (Box 6)
    - Allard, "Allard Special V–8 V–12"(SE: 1/1208), 1937; 1939 (Box 6)
    - Allard, Road Tests (Box 6)
    - Allard, Misc. (Box 6)
    - Alvis, "An Entirely New Sports Car – Speed Twenty"(SE: 1/877), 1932 (Box 6)
    - Alvis, "The 3½ Litre"(SE: 3/1210), 1935 (Sept.) (Box 6)
    - Alvis, "The 4.3 Litre"(SE: 6/1213), 1936 (Sept.) (Box 6)
    - Alvis, "...Short Chassis 4.3 Sports Tourer", 1937 (Aug. 3) (Box 6)
    - Alvis, "Masters of the King's Highway", 1939 (Box 6)
    - Alvis, "One of the World's Most Beautiful Cars...Three Litre", 1955–1957 (Box 6)
    - Alvis, "Graber", 1959 (Box 6)
    - Alvis, Photographs (Box 6)
    - Alvis, Road Tests (Box 6)
    - Alvis, Misc. (Box 6)
    - Armstrong/Siddeley, "Armstrong Whitworth Motor Cars"(SE: 1/194), 1912 (Box 6)
    - Armstrong/Siddeley, "J.D. Siddeley Type Deasy Motor Carriages"(SE: 2/195), 1912 (Box 6)
    - Armstrong/Siddeley, "Armstrong Siddeley"(SE: 3/878), 1929 (Box 6)
    - Armstrong/Siddeley, "Armstrong Siddeley Motors Limited"(SE: 4/879), 1931 (Box 6)
    - Armstrong/Siddeley, "Siddeley Special"(SE: 6/1217), 1933 (Box 6)
    - Armstrong/Siddeley, "The Siddeley Special 6", 1935 (June 7) (Box 6)
    - Armstrong/Siddeley, "Armstrong Siddeley", 1946 (Box 6)
    - Armstrong/Siddeley, Road Tests (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, "Aston–Martin 1932"(SE: 1/881) (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, "Britain's Best Sports Car", 1933–1934 (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, "The New 'Ulster' Model"(SE: 4/1220), 1934–1936 (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, "Achievement"(SE: 5/1221), 1936 (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, "The Aston–Martin 15/98"(SE: 6/1222), 1937–1938 (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, "2 Litre Sports Car", 1949 (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, "DB2 Sports Saloon", 1949 (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, "DB3S Competition Car", 1957 (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, "The David Brown Aston Martin DB4", 1958 (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, "The David Brown Aston Martin DB–5", 1964 (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, Photographs (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, Road Tests (Box 6)
    - Aston–Martin, Misc. (Box 6)
    - Atalanta, "Atalanta"(SE: 1/1223), 1937–1938 (Box 6)
    - Atalanta, Road Tests (Box 6)
    - Austin, Road Tests (Box 6)
    - Autovia, "The Luxury Car Modernised", 1937–1938 (Box 6)
    - Autovia, Road Tests (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The Three Litre Bentley"(SE: 1/510), 1919–1920 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The Three Litre Bentley"(SE: 3/512), 1921–1922 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The Three Litre Bentley" No. 7(SE: 6/515), 1924 (Oct.) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The Three Litre Bentley" No. 20, 1928 (Mar.) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The 4½ Litre Bentley" No. 30, 1929 (Oct.) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The New Eight Litre Bentley"(SE: 15/889) (facsimile), 1930 (Oct.) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley the Eight Litre" No. 35(SE: 16/890), 1931 (Feb.) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "A Preliminary Announcement", 1931 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Abridged Particulars Bentley, 3½ Litre"(SE: 1/1226), 1933–1934 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley, 3½ Litre"(SE: 3/1228), 1933–1934 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley, 3½ Litre, Some Opinions"(SE: 4/1229), 1934 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley, 3½ Litre"(SE: 5/1230), 1934 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Motor Dicta – A Weekend", 1934 (June 13) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Driver–Controlled Suspension...", 1935 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "3½ Litre Bentley Drop–Head Coupe", 1935 (Dec. 10) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "A Prince Among Cars", 1936 (June 13) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley, the Silent Sports Car"(SE: 7/1232), 1936 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley 4¼ Litre All-Weather (4 Doors)", 1937 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley Sports Tourer 4¼ Litre", 1937 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley, the Silent Sports Car", 1938 (Box 6)